http://www.mainewebworks.com/resources/privacy

Privacy Policy
The privacy of our visitors and clients is important to our working relationship. You do not have to give us personal information to visit our site. Any personally identifying information collected will be used only in connection with Maine Webworks and the services we provide to our clients.
Links to websites outside of our website pages are beyond our control; please refer to the privacy statements belonging to the sites linked to this site.
Maine Webworks will protect the personal information that you share with us. We do not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information to third parties.
However, we may ask our clients to be a reference of our services to our prospective clients interested in our services and will only do so with permission which may be granted to us by our work for hire agreement.
While we will make every attempt to protect the personal information that you share with us, electronic mail is not absolutely secure against interception. If your communication contains sensitive information, you may want to send it by postal mail.
Please note, several search engines require company information such as your url, email and contact name.
We will only supply the information required to submit your web site as according to their submission policies to aid in your efforts to be indexed by search engines.
Home
Portfolio
Services
Packages
Resources
Partnerships
Contact
© Copyright 2003 - 2020 Maine Webworks. All Rights Reserved.
This website is monitored using the following services:
Free website uptime monitor from basicstate.com  |  Free website monitoring by mon.itor.us
